<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amps on SpashtNews</title>
    <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amps on SpashtNews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2019. SpashtNews - All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 22:04:54 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://spashtnews.com/amp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Victory - A historic record for India against South Africa </title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/great-victory-india-against-south-africa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 22:04:54 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/great-victory-india-against-south-africa/</guid>
      <description>What a victory has it been for the &amp;ldquo;Men in White&amp;rdquo;. This is India’s biggest victory over South Africa by an innings and 137 runs. To add icing on the cake this is India’s eleventh consecutive home series win which is a new world record.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PM Modi and President Xi meet at Mamallapuram to discuss a new era of Indo China relations</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/pm-modi-president-xi-indo-china-meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 23:21:59 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/pm-modi-president-xi-indo-china-meet/</guid>
      <description>The second informal summit between Prime Minister Narendra Modi and China’s President Xi Jinping began on Friday at Mamallapuram. The first summit took place in Wuhan in April 2018 in the wake of the Doklam crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to elections in Maharashtra and Haryana - But where does the opposition stand?</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/bjp-elections-maharashtra-haryana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 06:14:29 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/bjp-elections-maharashtra-haryana/</guid>
      <description>The bugle has been blown by the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) post abrogation of Article 370 for elections to be held in two states of Haryana and Maharashtra which are being ruled by BJP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBI cuts repo rate by 25 basis points to 5.15%</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/rbi-cuts-repo-rate-by-25-bps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 23:31:04 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/rbi-cuts-repo-rate-by-25-bps/</guid>
      <description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) on Friday announced a decision to cut Key Policy Rate by 25 Basis Points to 5.15%. This will help stimulate consumer sentiments in the upcoming festive season, which augurs well for the real estate business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Pressure on India to lift sanctions in Kashmir Valley : Action and not words required</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/international-pressure-lift-sanctions-kashmir-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 21:15:18 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/international-pressure-lift-sanctions-kashmir-valley/</guid>
      <description>Anantnag district witnessed a grenade attack that has left fourteen seriously injured. The grenade attack was carried out by the suspected militants yesterday near the Deputy Commissioner of Police (DCP) office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some good news coming from across the border in respect to Kartarpur Corridor</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/manmohan-singh-to-visit-pakistan-for-kartarpur-corridor-inauguration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 10:17:45 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/manmohan-singh-to-visit-pakistan-for-kartarpur-corridor-inauguration/</guid>
      <description>The Chief Minister of Punjab, Captain Amarinder Singh has extended an invitation to the former Prime Minister Manmohan Singh and present Prime Minister Narendra Modi to attend 550th birth anniversary of Guru Nanak, the founder of Sikhism next month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mahatma of the Nation : Gandhiji’s two weapons, Satyagraha and Non Violence</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/mahatma-gandhi-150-birth-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 10:17:45 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/mahatma-gandhi-150-birth-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>The entire nation is celebrating the 150th birth anniversary of the greatest Indian ever, Mohandas Karamchand Gandhi, the Father of our Nation. Gandhiji was a visionary and led the Indian Freedom Struggle with two main weapons of Satyagraha and Non Violence, which inspired many political leaders and mass movements in many countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel in the crown of Indian politics, Lal Bahadur Shastri was one of the finest Prime Minister we ever had</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/lal-bahadur-shastri-115-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:56 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/lal-bahadur-shastri-115-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Lal Bahadur Shastri was the second Prime Minister of India. Born on 02nd October, 1904 in Mughalsarai, his father’s name was Sharda Prasad Shrivastav. He served as India’s Prime Minister after the death of Jawaharlal Nehru from 09th June, 1964 to 11th January, 1966 for a period of 18 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post US Summit, India’s relations with the other powerhouse countries of the world needs introspection</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/india-relation-with-powerhouse-countries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 22:26:50 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/india-relation-with-powerhouse-countries/</guid>
      <description>The past one week was one of the busiest schedules witnessed by the entire nation in respect to Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s US visit. After his speech at Houston, subsequent address to the United Nations General Assembly and Bloomberg Summit, India’s key message on Climate Change, Terrorism and Economic Strategies were on special mention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PM Modi discusses development programs whereas PM Imran Khan propagates war threat</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/modi-unga-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 20:46:10 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/modi-unga-speech/</guid>
      <description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s address to United Nations General Assembly (UNGA) was an ambitious one. The PM laid stress on various socio economic aspects and its development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How impactful is the corporate tax deduction going to be?</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/corporate-tax-deduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 19:37:01 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/corporate-tax-deduction/</guid>
      <description>There are clear positives to the Diwali gift of the corporate tax cuts of the government. Before this announcement industries with exemption paid more than 25% corporate tax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All words no action: Climate change is no longer a doomsday prophecy, it’s a reality!</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/climate-change-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 20:03:51 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/climate-change-reality/</guid>
      <description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi has called for a Global People’s Movement to bring about behavioural change to tackle &amp;ldquo;Climate Change&amp;rdquo;. Howdy Modi is over now. The Prime Minister should now attend some serious business and his words must match his actions towards steps taken to address climate change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Howdy Modi : Prime Minister Modi plays host to President Trump in the United States</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/modi-plays-host-to-trump-in-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 20:32:14 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/modi-plays-host-to-trump-in-us/</guid>
      <description>It was a grand welcome for Prime Minister Narendra Modi as he kicked off his United States visit from Houston. The event was witnessed by fifty thousand Indians who had booked their seats much in advance to be a part of this mega event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Day of Peace - Let’s make this world a place of peace</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/international-day-of-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 22:01:16 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/international-day-of-peace/</guid>
      <description>International Day of Peace is celebrated on 21st September every year. To inaugurate the day, the United Nations peace bell is rung at the United Nations Headquarters in New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#34;Anands&#34; of Chinmayanand : Such Swamis are a disgrace to the society </title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/swami-chinmayanand-arrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 00:35:08 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/swami-chinmayanand-arrest/</guid>
      <description>Finally Swami Chinmayanand has been arrested after the victim threatened to kill herself if the Special Investigation Team (SIT) did not arrest the accused. The BJP leader is a rape accused of a law student and was arrested today by the SIT from his Ashram.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clean India Green India</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/clean-india-green-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:01:32 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/clean-india-green-india/</guid>
      <description>One step taken up by the Government of India for a cleaner and greener environment needs mention. The ban of single use plastics will help enormously for a clean environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mob Lynching - Don’t hate what you don’t understand</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/mob-lynching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 23:46:43 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/mob-lynching/</guid>
      <description>Mob Lynching refers to killing someone with an &amp;ldquo;alleged&amp;rdquo; offence without following any due process of law. Misunderstanding arising from ignorance breeds fear and fear is the greatest enemy of peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviving Indian Economy</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/reviving-indian-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 20:49:07 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/reviving-indian-economy/</guid>
      <description>The increase in Gross Domestic Product (GDP) is a parameter to measure the country&amp;rsquo;s economic growth. The GDP is defined as the combined value of all goods and services produced in a country annually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kashmir Issue : A Chronological Description</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/kashmir-issue-chronological-desc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 23:32:04 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/kashmir-issue-chronological-desc/</guid>
      <description>The Kashmir dispute dates back to 1947. The Britishers before leaving India followed a &amp;lsquo;divide and rule&amp;rsquo; policy on religious sentiments which led to the Partition of India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravish Kumar touches the pinnacle of journalism - Conferred the Ramon Magsaysay Award</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/ravish-kumar-pinnacle-of-journalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 20:14:09 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/ravish-kumar-pinnacle-of-journalism/</guid>
      <description>What a proud moment for Ravish Kumar. We are extremely delighted that the prestigious Magsaysay Award for free and Spasht journalism has been conferred on him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Om and Cows solve for REAL issues?</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/can-om-and-cows-solve-real-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 20:13:39 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/can-om-and-cows-solve-real-issues/</guid>
      <description>The kind of address Prime Minister Narendra Modi made today in Mathura, Uttar Pradesh was a clear indication that he is back in the election mode which are going to be held in Haryana, Maharashtra and Jharkhand this year and Bihar next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNHRC meet at Geneva on Kashmir issue</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/unhrc-meet-geneva-on-kashmir-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 21:33:51 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/unhrc-meet-geneva-on-kashmir-issue/</guid>
      <description>A significant meeting is going to be held between India and Pakistan at Geneva, Switzerland today on the issue of Kashmir at United Nations Human Rights Council (UNHRC) after international pressure on India to ease the situation in Jammu and Kashmir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission Moon: Chandrayaan 2</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/mission-moon-chandrayaan-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 10:49:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/mission-moon-chandrayaan-2/</guid>
      <description>My memory takes me back to the famous lines that were once recited by the former Prime Minister and one of the most dynamic Prime Ministers ever, Shri Atal Bihari Vajpayee that read -</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chidambaram Saga Continues</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/chidambaram-saga-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 22:40:01 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/chidambaram-saga-continues/</guid>
      <description>The verdict has come. Former Finance Minister, P Chidambaram has been jailed for fourteen days of judicial custody. This is a major blow to former Finance Minister and his continuous efforts to evade jail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Progressive Teacher : Importance of Teacher Student Relationship</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/importance-teacher-student-relationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:14:49 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/importance-teacher-student-relationship/</guid>
      <description>GururBrahma GururVishnu Gururdevo Maheshwara GururSakshaat ParaBrahma Tasmay ShriGurvey Namah
Guru - Formed of two words Gu - Darkness and Ru - Remover, someone who destroys darkness in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bleeding Indian Economy</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/the-bleeding-indian-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 20:38:36 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/the-bleeding-indian-economy/</guid>
      <description>Let’s go back 90 years in the year 1929 - the year when all across the world the stock markets had crashed down heavily and the world was staring at the worst recession ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decision on Chidambaram’s interim bail soon</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/decision-on-chidambaram-bail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 19:17:46 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/decision-on-chidambaram-bail/</guid>
      <description>The latest on P Chidambaram is that the Supreme Court has asked the trial court to consider Chidambaram’s plea for an interim bail in the INX Media Case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worrying state of the Indian economy at 5% GDP growth</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/worrying-state-of-indian-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:01:46 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/worrying-state-of-indian-economy/</guid>
      <description>Indian economy is heading towards a winter recession in a state of trepidation. Anybody who thinks that we are not facing a serious economic crisis is turning a blind eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security at Gujarat Coastal Areas after Terror threat</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/security-at-gujarat-coastal-areas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 21:26:11 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/security-at-gujarat-coastal-areas/</guid>
      <description>India has reacted sharply to Islamabad after its missile test and warned that they should not encourage escalation of terrorism in the region. Pakistan has time and again given very irresponsible statements in respect to Kashmir which is not going well with the Indian government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fate of People in Assam Post NRC</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/fate-of-people-in-assam-post-nrc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 17:41:10 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/fate-of-people-in-assam-post-nrc/</guid>
      <description>The National Register of Citizens (NRC) is a register containing the names of all genuine citizens of India. It was first prepared in 1951. As of now, the NRC is being updated for the state of Assam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jio: Creating disruption in the telecom industry</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/jio-disruption-telecom-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 14:01:16 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/jio-disruption-telecom-industry/</guid>
      <description>Digital revolution is growing at an exponential pace in India. Chairman and Managing Director of Reliance Industries, Mukesh Ambani, left no stone unturned to be a part of such exponential growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan&#39;s Nuclear Threat</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/pakistan-nuclear-threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 22:01:47 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/pakistan-nuclear-threat/</guid>
      <description>After it became clear to Pakistan’s Prime Minister Imran Khan that the USA was not going to intervene in Kashmir, he has become a restless person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Economic Slowdown - How well is India prepared?</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/the-economic-slowdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 21:28:25 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/the-economic-slowdown/</guid>
      <description>For the time being, Kashmir and Article 370 can take a back seat. There is a more serious business to be taken care of. A heavy debate is going on in the country about one of the worst economic slow-down in probably more than four decades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Silent Valley</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/the-silent-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 22:15:44 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/the-silent-valley/</guid>
      <description>US President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s intervention in Kashmir is all over, after he agreed that it is a bilateral issue to be resolved by India and Pakistan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fading Glitter of Gold</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/the-fading-glitter-of-gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 22:34:59 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/the-fading-glitter-of-gold/</guid>
      <description>All that glitters is not gold NOW for a common man. The yellow metal prices continue to rise further touching a ₹40,000 mark today.
How does gold affect the economy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New World Champ</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/the-new-world-champ/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 21:49:56 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/the-new-world-champ/</guid>
      <description>Pusarla V Sindhu did the country proud by becoming the first Indian to win the coveted gold medal at the World Badminton Championship held at Basle, Switzerland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chidambaram&#39;s Tryst With Destiny</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/amp/chidambaram-tryst-with-destiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/amp/chidambaram-tryst-with-destiny/</guid>
      <description>What a drama has been created by the top echelons of our society and by that I mean CBI - the most trusted investigating agency of a democratic India.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>