<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Narendra Modi on SpashtNews</title>
    <link>https://spashtnews.com/tags/narendra-modi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Narendra Modi on SpashtNews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2019. SpashtNews - All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 20:46:10 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://spashtnews.com/tags/narendra-modi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PM Modi discusses development programs whereas PM Imran Khan propagates war threat</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/modi-unga-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 20:46:10 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/modi-unga-speech/</guid>
      <description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s address to United Nations General Assembly (UNGA) was an ambitious one. The PM laid stress on various socio economic aspects and its development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Howdy Modi : Prime Minister Modi plays host to President Trump in the United States</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/modi-plays-host-to-trump-in-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 20:32:14 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/modi-plays-host-to-trump-in-us/</guid>
      <description>It was a grand welcome for Prime Minister Narendra Modi as he kicked off his United States visit from Houston. The event was witnessed by fifty thousand Indians who had booked their seats much in advance to be a part of this mega event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Om and Cows solve for REAL issues?</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/can-om-and-cows-solve-real-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 20:13:39 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/can-om-and-cows-solve-real-issues/</guid>
      <description>The kind of address Prime Minister Narendra Modi made today in Mathura, Uttar Pradesh was a clear indication that he is back in the election mode which are going to be held in Haryana, Maharashtra and Jharkhand this year and Bihar next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNHRC meet at Geneva on Kashmir issue</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/unhrc-meet-geneva-on-kashmir-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 21:33:51 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/unhrc-meet-geneva-on-kashmir-issue/</guid>
      <description>A significant meeting is going to be held between India and Pakistan at Geneva, Switzerland today on the issue of Kashmir at United Nations Human Rights Council (UNHRC) after international pressure on India to ease the situation in Jammu and Kashmir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Silent Valley</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/the-silent-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 22:15:44 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/the-silent-valley/</guid>
      <description>US President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s intervention in Kashmir is all over, after he agreed that it is a bilateral issue to be resolved by India and Pakistan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>