<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BJP on SpashtNews</title>
    <link>https://spashtnews.com/tags/bjp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BJP on SpashtNews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2019. SpashtNews - All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 09:06:24 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://spashtnews.com/tags/bjp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Collision in Coalition</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/collision-in-coalition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 09:06:24 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/collision-in-coalition/</guid>
      <description>Amidst criticism from the Opposition, Governor of Maharashtra BS Koshiyari clamped President’s rule in the State when it became clear that no party was in a position to form a government, thus putting to an end nearly three weeks of political instability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maharashtra and Haryana may influence the fate of the depleted Opposition?</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/maharashtra-haryana-assembly-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 23:22:50 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/maharashtra-haryana-assembly-elections/</guid>
      <description>A major dip was registered in the Assembly Elections held in the two states of Haryana and Maharashtra. The total turnout was 60% in Maharashtra and 65% in Haryana compared to 63% and 76% respectively in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ahead of Assembly Polls let’s discuss the REAL ISSUES instead of mudslinging the Opposition</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/ahead-of-assembly-polls-real-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 01:35:36 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/ahead-of-assembly-polls-real-issues/</guid>
      <description>The national interest is once again at the forefront of the election campaign being carried out by the Prime Minister Narendra Modi. In yet another sharp attack on the Opposition combining the Congress and Nationalist Congress Party (NCP), the Prime Minister accused them of speaking against the national interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to elections in Maharashtra and Haryana - But where does the opposition stand?</title>
      <link>https://spashtnews.com/bjp-elections-maharashtra-haryana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 06:14:29 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spashtnews.com/bjp-elections-maharashtra-haryana/</guid>
      <description>The bugle has been blown by the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) post abrogation of Article 370 for elections to be held in two states of Haryana and Maharashtra which are being ruled by BJP.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>